准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
果仁巧克力
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
嗨  邮递员
Hi, mailman
那好吧  明天见
Okay, see you tomorrow
信来了
The mail's here
收到什么了
What did you get?
来看下
Let's see
小蜗  小蜗
Gary, Gary
有本杂志
A magazine
奢华生活文摘
真是奇怪  我不记得
That's funny, I don't remember
自己有订过奢华生活文摘啊
subscribing to Fancy Living Digest
你看这书里光鲜亮丽地描绘了
Look at these glossy depictions
更高级的生活标准
of a higher standard of living
这位已经富到
This guy's so rich
都有个游泳池中池了
he has a swimming pool in his swimming pool
这位还有鞋
This guy's got shoes
快给我
Give me that
偷我邮件是吧
Stealing my mail, eh?
你们应该庆幸我没有去举报了你们
You're lucky I don't report you to the authorities
章鱼哥
Hey, Squidward
那杂志里的阔佬是怎么弄到钱的
how do those people get all that money?
他们是创业家
They're entrepreneurs
专门卖东西的
They sell things to people
卖的哪种东西
What kind of things?
我哪知道
How should I know?
反正是大家想买的
Things people want to buy
别乱动我的邮件
Now, keep your paws off my mail
有了  派大星
That's it, Patrick
我们得去当创业家
We got to become entrepreneurs
会伤着我吗
Is that gonna hurt?
派大星  快直接回答我
Quick, Patrick, without thinking
如果你现在要啥就有啥
if you could have anything in the world right now
会要什么
what would it be?
要再来点想问题的时间
More time for thinking
不行  要实在的
No, something real
要物件  可以付钱买的东西
an item, something you would pay for
巧克力棒吗
A chocolate bar?
真是好点子  派大星
That's a great idea, Pat
就来当巧克力棒上门推销员吧
We'll be traveling chocolate bar salesmen
便宜货超市
奢华生活
Fancy living
我们来了
here we come
给这两个撞业家让条道吧
Make way for a couple of "entrepe-nooers"
派大星  到了
Okay, Patrick, this is it
我们奢华生活之路的第一步
the first step on our road to living fancy
跟我来就行
Just follow my lead
下午好  先生
Good afternoon, sir
你有没有兴趣要来点巧克力
Could we interest you in some chocolate?
巧克力
Chocolate?
你们是不是说了  巧克力
Did you say "chocolate"?
对的  先生
Yes, sir
要加果仁的还是不加果仁的
With or without nuts?
巧克力
Chocolate?
Chocolate
巧克力
刚刚那第一位不算
Okay, that first guy didn't count
这才是我们真正的第一步
This is our real first step
早安  先生
Good morning, sir
要买点巧克力吗
Would you like to buy some chocolate?
是巧克力棒吗
Chocolate bars, eh?
是啊  我们是巧克力棒推销员
Yes, sir, we are chocolate bar salesmen
我看你们俩推销员做得还挺一般
A couple a mediocre salesmen, if you ask me
这样运送商品是不对的
That's no way to carry your merchandise
不行不行  那样错了
No, no, no, wrong
你们想当优良推销员吧
You guys want to be good salesmen, right?
那当然了  先生
Most certainly sir
只要是有点自尊的巧克力棒推销员
Well, no self-respecting candy bar salesman
都会带上这种玩意
would be caught dead without one of these
这什么东西
What is it?
是巧克力棒袋  你们两个笨蛋
It's a candy bar bag, you knucklehead
精心特制
It's specially designed
且有丝绒内衬  舒适安放每条巧克力
to cradle each candy bar in velvet-lined comfort
但是
But
简直是浪费我时间
I'm wasting my time
你们用不着袋子
You don't need these bags
我们要用
We need them
再见了  小子们
So long, boys
祝你们卖得愉快
Happy hunting
真是傻子
Suckers
奢华生活  我们来了
Fancy living, here we come
试下下一家
Let's try next door
有事吗
Yes?
你不是卖我们巧克力棒袋的那位吗
Say, weren't you the same guy
who sold us these candy bar bags?
我
I
不记得了
don't recall
不过看样子
But it looks to me
你们俩身上袋子还挺多
like you fellas have got a lot of bags there
你们两个少女杀手可聪明了
You two lady-killers are too smart to be
必须要有我专利认证的
without one of my patented
巧克力棒袋收纳用袋
candy bar bag carrying bags
我们要买二十个
We'll take 20
你们俩好心年轻人要干嘛
What can I do for you two nice young men?
我们在卖巧克力棒
We're selling chocolate bars
要买一根吗
Like to buy one?
听起来好像还挺好吃
That sounds heavenly
我要买一根
I'll take one
一根巧克力棒马上来
One chocolate bar coming up
肯定就在里面的
I know they're in here somewhere
我没空陪你们闹
I don't have time for this
找到了
I got it
巧克力棒卖给漂亮的
One chocolate bar for the nice
巧克力
Chocolate
小姐
lady
巧克力
Chocolate
小餐馆
我们表现不太好啊  派大星
We're not doing so well, Patrick
得要换个办法
We need a new approach
换个策略
a new tactic
有了
I got it
来裸奔吧
let's get naked
不行  等卖房再裸奔
No, let's save that for when we're selling real estate
肯定有门道
There must be something
之前为什么要买那些袋子
What was the reason we bought those bags?
他说我们一般
He said we were mediocre
对了
That's it
他让我们觉得特别了
He made us feel special
对啊  确实
Yeah, he did
我回去再买点袋子来
I'm going back to buy more bags
先别走  派大星
No, wait, Patrick
要不我们试下友善待人吧
Why don't we try being nice?
好啊
Okay
别忘了  派大星
Remember, Patrick
讨好顾客
flatter the customer
让他自我感觉良好
Make him feel good
怎么了
Hello?
我爱你
I love you
你好像做得有点过头了
You laid it on a teensy thick there, old pal
我来试试
Let me try
求你们了
Please
走开
Go away
你近来如何
How ya doin'?
我近来如何
How am I doing?
要买点巧克力吗
Wanna buy some chocolate?
讨好到人家了
We got him now
抱歉  巧克力含糖
Sorry, chocolate has sugar
起 泡
糖会转化成发胖的脂肪
and sugar turns to bubbling fat
对不对啊  爱吃巧克力的
Isn't that right, lover boy?
好痒啊
It tickles
你们也看得出来我不碰巧克力了
As you can see, me and chocolate no longer hang
十三岁的我
照片一张五块钱
You can keep that for five bucks
我要买十张
I'll take ten
连一根巧克力棒都没有卖出去
We haven't sold one chocolate bar
感觉我们太容易分心了
I have a feeling we're too easily distracted
我们现在来约定
Let's make a pact right now
到下一家要专心推销
that we will stay focused on selling at the next house
什么
What?
握手约定
Let's shake on it
你刚刚有说话吗
Did you say something?
派大星别忘了  专心看
Remember, Patrick, focus
有事吗
Yes?
下午好  先生
Good afternoon, sir
我们在卖巧克力棒
We're selling chocolate bars
这胖子怎么在盯着我
Why is Chubby here staring at me?
专心看
Focusing
给我滚回去
Back up, Jack
你这家还真不错啊
Nice place you got here
不明白哪里做错了
I can't understand what we're doing wrong
我什么都明白不了
I can't understand anything
推销这行肯定还有别的什么秘诀
There must be something to this selling game
就只有咱不懂
that we're just not getting
别人就都懂  比方看那个
Other people do it, I mean, look at that
快吃藤壶薯片
美味可口
快吃藤壶薯片  美味可口
"Eat Barnacle Chips, they're delicious"
多半难吃死了
They are most certainly not delicious
用我的吃法就好吃了
Not the way I use them
结果这薯片一天能卖好几百万包
Yet they sell millions of bags a day
可能不搞夸张的话
Well, maybe if they didn't stretch the truth
就卖不了这么多了
they wouldn't sell as many
对了  派大星
That's it, Patrick
我们得搞夸张
We've got to stretch the truth
巧克力
Chocolate
一起合作
We'll work as a team
我来给这客人预热预热
Let me get this customer warmed up
然后你来把这家拿下
and then you come in for the kill
拿下
The kill
有事吗
Yes?
你好啊  年轻的小姐
Hello, young lady
我们在卖巧克力
We're selling chocolate
你妈在家吗
Is your mother home?
妈
Mom
干嘛
What?
叫什么叫
What's all that yelling?
你就等不及要我去死  是不是
You just can't wait for me to die, can you?
他们在卖巧克力
They're selling chocolate
巧克力
Chocolate?
对
Yeah
什么
What?
在卖什么
What are they selling?
巧克力
Chocolates
卖什么
What?
巧克力
Chocolates
我听不清
I can't hear you
他们在卖巧克力
They're selling chocolates
他们在卖巧克力吗
They're selling chocolate?
对
Yeah
巧克力啊
Chocolate?
我还记得巧克力刚发明出来那会儿
I remember when they first invented chocolate
那甜甜的巧克力
Sweet, sweet chocolate
我向来都恨死了
I always hated it
可这种巧克力不是用来吃的
But this chocolate's not for eating
是用来
It's for
要把它涂在身上
You rub it on your skin
就能长生不老了
and it makes you live forever
别别别
No, no, no
你说长生不老吗
Live forever, you say?
我买了
I'll take one
快点  懒惰鬼玛丽
Come on, you lazy Mary
快把那巧克力涂我身上
Start rubbing me with that chocolate
我恨你们
I hate you
要是继续搞夸张
If we keep exaggerating the truth
马上就能有奢华生活了
we'll be fancy-living in no time
说谎万岁
Hooray for lying
可以让你长头发
It'll make your hair grow
太棒了
Great
我老婆就想要长胡子
My wife's trying to grow a beard
可以让你言语谈吐变聪明
It'll make you sound smart
我要买二十块
I'll take 20
可以让你脸不再变丑
It'll keep your face from getting any uglier
正好
Just in time
可以让你飞
They make you fly
可以让你恋爱
You'll fall in love
可以给世界带来和平
They'll bring world peace
可以让你穿墙
You'll walk through walls
可以让你统治世界
You'll rule the world
这回说的谎肯定最强
This'll be the best lie yet
对啊
Yeah
这位一定会特别同情我们
This guy will feel so sorry for us
然后就把咱所有巧克力都买走
he'll have to buy all of our chocolate
你们有什么事情吗
What can I do for you boys?
先生好
Hello, sir
你想要买巧克力棒吗
would you like to buy a chocolate bar?
我们要做手术
We need an operation
真的吗
Really?
同病相怜啊
Small world
你们是怎么了
What's the matter with you guys?
我们有头部外伤跟内出血
We've got some head trauma and internal bleeding
有些家伙就是运气好
Some guys have all the luck
我生来就有易碎的骨头跟柔弱的皮肤
I was born with glass bones and paper skin
每天早上我都会断腿
Every morning I break my legs
每天下午我都会断胳膊
and every afternoon I break my arms
晚上  我疼得睡不着
At night I lie awake in agony
直至心脏病让我昏迷
until my heart attacks put me to sleep
不好
Oh, no
派大星  咱们快帮帮人家
Quick, Patrick, let's help him
小心点
Careful
轻轻放下
Put him down gently
真可怜
Poor, poor man
有什么办法
If there's anything
怎样都行
anything
能帮得上你吗
We can do to help you
有一样东西
There is one thing
你们也想象得到
As you can well imagine
我的医疗费特别的高
my medical bills are extremely high
不过幸好  我活命的条件
but luckily I'm able to keep myself alive
就是卖
by selling
巧克力棒
chocolate bars
真是心善
Such nice boys
这下我心里可真是舒坦
It does my heart good
骗到了这两个顶级白痴
to con a couple of class-A sucker-roonies like those two
先别误会  派大星
Don't get me wrong, Patrick
虽然能救他一命是不错
it's great that we helped him out
可是镇上已经没几个买巧克力的了
but there's no one left in town to sell chocolate bars to
认了吧  派大星
Let's face it, Patrick
我们是废物
we're failures
这我能接受
I can live with that
我们还是改名叫何苦兄弟吧
Let's change our names to "Why" and "Bother"
巧克力
Chocolate
不要  别伤害我们
No, no, don't hurt us
求你了
Please
终于啊
Finally
我一整天都可想着要逮着你们
I've been trying to catch you boys all day
既然我逮着你们了
Now that I've got you right where I want you
我想买下你们所有的巧克力
I'd like to buy all your chocolate
感谢您的惠顾
Thank you for your patronage
我们过上奢华生活了吗  海绵宝宝
Are we living the fancy life yet, SpongeBob?
还没呢  兄弟
Not yet, pally
首先得把钱都花掉
First we got to spend all the money
可要先把钱花在哪
But what are we going to spend it on?
奢华
晚上好  先生
Good evening, sir
来张单人桌
Table for one, please
对不起  整间餐厅已经租给了
Sorry, but the whole restaurant has been rented
一家私人聚会
to a private party
可我只有今晚才能放纵奢华啊
But it's my only night to be fancy
谁这么有钱  能租下来一整间餐厅
Who could afford to rent out the whole restaurant?
是对富创业家  以及他们的对象
A couple of rich entrepreneurs and their dates
那么  你们两位小姐认识多久了
So, how long have you two ladies known each other?
什么
What?
他说什么了
What did he say?
美人鱼战士
和企鹅男孩
分镜总监
分镜
翻译: 1440kHz
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
客串
配音 美人鱼战士
配音 企鹅男孩
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩的全新冒险
The New Adventures of Mermaidman and Barnacleboy
在熟悉的一家餐厅里
In a familiar restaurant
在熟悉的小镇一角里
in a familiar part of town
蟹堡王
发出了沮丧的呼声
a call goes out in frustration
能不能给我快点
Will you hurry up?
这呼声通常能
A call that would normally
被裤头村的半退休守护者所回答
be answered by Bikini Bottom's semiretired champions
除非他们就是引起问题的人
If they weren't the ones causing the problem
我想想
Now, let's see
我要一份
I want a
不对
no
我要一份
I want a
菜单
不对
No
先生  能不能赶紧点餐
Sir, will you please order already?
你害整条队都不动了
You're holding up the line
美人鱼战士  来份蟹黄堡
Hey, Mermaidman, get a Krabby Patty
我决定好了
I've made my decision
给我来份蟹黄堡
One Krabby Patty for me
给这小朋友来份儿童堡
and a Pip-squeak Patty for the boy
给老子等一下
Now, wait just a darn minute
我不要儿童堡
I don't want a Pip-squeak Patty
我要成人尺寸的蟹黄堡
I want an adult-sized Krabby Patty
蟹黄堡对你来说太大了
The Krabby Patty is too big for you
你可吃不完
You'll never finish it
知不知道你这是在干什么
Don't you see what you're doing?
你这是在把我当小孩子
You're treating me like a child
小朋友都是胃口大  肚子小
The boy's eyes are bigger than his stomach
这也是问题所在
And that's another thing
我不是小朋友
I'm not a boy
我老到
I'm so old
连老年斑上的皱纹都长毛了
I've got hairs growing out of the wrinkles
on my liver spots
一份儿童堡
One Pip-squeak Patty
还有围兜跟高脚椅
And your bib and high chair
老子68岁了  要蟹黄堡
I'm 68 years old and I want a Krabby Patty
你的儿童堡要冷了
Your Pip-squeak is getting cold
要不要我喂你
Shall I feed you?
自个吃吧  死老头
Feed this, old man
我已经不想死死跟在
I'm tired of playing second banana
某位胸罩男身后了
to a man who wears a bra
从今往后要叫我企鹅男人
From now on, I want to be called Barnacleman
我再也不保护不尊重我的民众了
And I'm through with protecting citizens
that don't respect me
我尊重你  企鹅男人
I respect you, Barnacleman
是企鹅男孩  我
That's Barnacleboy, I
我是说男人
I mean man
不管你们了
Forget you people
如果不把我当英雄尊重
I say if you're not going to give me any respect as a hero
那么只能把我当恶人尊重
then maybe you'll give me respect as a villain
这个恶人特别
A villain who is
邪恶
evil
Evil?
邪恶
Evil
我要去投靠黑暗一方
I'm crossing over to the dark side
我干嘛要浪费钱把整家店都照亮
Why should I waste money lighting the whole store?
裤头村
就要对你坏
有人说到邪恶了吗
Did someone say "evil"?
我的海上漏油啊
Holy oil spill
是美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩的夙敌
It's Mermaidman and Barnacleboy's arch enemies
射线恶魔和肮脏泡泡
Man Ray and the Dirty Bubble
晚安了  老山羊
Nighty-night, you old goat
晚安了
Nighty-night
你能帮我盖被子吗
Will you tuck me in?
我们打断你们悲惨又毫无意义的生活
We interrupt your bleak and meaningless lives
新闻快报
插播本则特别报道
for this special news break
射线恶魔
Man Ray
第一航海银行
肮脏泡泡
the Dirty Bubble
还有现在投靠黑暗一方的  企鹅男孩
And now, playing for the dark side, Barnacleboy
企鹅男人
Barnacleman
在裤头村犯下了一系列滔天大罪
Have been committing a series of crimes
throughout Bikini Bottom
我要抓到你们这些小屁孩
I'll get you crazy kids
这三个人将他们新建的联盟命名作
These three have named their new alliance
柠 檬
恶人皆为大废物
Every Villain Is Lemons
亦作邪恶帮
otherwise known as EVIL
我们该怎么办
What can we do?
这场罪恶浪潮将何时停止
When will this crime wave end?
怎样才能击败邪恶帮
How will we defeat the EVIL?
我为什么要向你们问这些问题
Why am I asking you all these questions?
美人鱼战士  你在哪
Mermaidman, where are you?
我就在这
I'm right here
不必担心  良民们
Don't worry, good citizens
没有东西会阻止我击败邪恶帮
nothing will stop me from defeating the EVIL
没有东西
Nothing
冰淇淋
Ice cream?
我爱冰淇淋
I love ice cream
来两球加麦麸粒的梅子味冰淇淋
A double scoop of prune with bran sprinkles
麸爆
每次都害我拉肚子
Goes right through me every time
你还是放弃吧  美人鱼战士
You might as well give up, Mermaidman
我们这边有三个  你那边只有一个
There's three of us and only one of you
你没机会赢
You don't stand a chance
你没事吧  美人鱼战士
Are you okay, Mermaidman?
以你一个人的力量要怎么打败他们仨
How are you going to beat
all three of those guys by yourself?
说得对
You're right
我放弃
I give up
你不能放弃
You can't give up
我们来帮你怎么样
What if we help you?
不行  这就是一馊主意
No, no, that's a terrible idea
那要是你们来帮我怎么样
But what if you help me?
好啊
Okay
那么  谁想要拯救世界
So, who wants to save the world?
我想要
I do
我不要
I don't
不要也得要
Yes, you do
世界没了就等于钱没了
No world means no money
快去拯救世界  不然开除你
Now, go save the world or you're fired
就这么定了
Then it's settled
去美人鱼基地
To the Mermalair
美人鱼基地
The Mermalair
这些衣服属于原版
These costumes belonged to the original
国际超级老相识正义联盟
International Justice League
of Super Acquaintances
正联是史上最英勇的英雄
The I.J.L.S.A. were the most heroic heroes ever
国际老相识正义联盟
你们正联也有史上最棒的午餐盒
And you had the best lunch box, too
一旦穿上这些衣服
Once you put on these costumes
他们的超能力就会归你们了
their fantastic powers will become yours
超能力不是这样起效的吧
I didn't think super-powers worked that way
就是这样
Sure
超能力都蕴含在衣服里面
Power's all in the costume
不然干嘛要穿彩色内衣到处跑
Why else would we run around in colored undies?
我倒能想三个充分理由来解释了
I can think of three good reasons
飞毛腿
The Quickster
超能力就是跑步速度非常
With the uncanny ability to run really
快
quick
要看我跑上那座山再跑回来吗
Want to see me run to that mountain and back?
要看我再跑一次吗
You want to see me do it again?
怒火船长
Captain Magma
惹他生气  他就会爆发岩浆
Get him angry and he's bound to erupt
喀拉喀托大爆发
Krakatoa
弹性胖胖
The Elastic Waistband
能够把身体拉成各种神奇的形状
Able to stretch his body
into fantastic shapes and forms
我终于可以摸到脚趾头了
I can finally touch my toes
还有无影小姐
And Miss Appear
现在看得到她  现在看不到了
Now you see her, now you don't
这身会不会显胖
Does this outfit make me look fat?
国际超级老相识正义联盟
The International Justice League
of Super Acquaintances
维亚康姆的子公司
A subsidiary of Viacom
[ 维亚康姆：《海绵宝宝》出品公司 ]
那就这么定了
So, it's agreed
点一份奶酪匹萨
We'll get one cheese pizza
一份辣香肠蘑菇匹萨  一份橄榄匹萨
one with pepperoni and mushrooms, and one with olives
超级老相识们  请求支援
Super Acquaintances, we need your help
我的比目鱼啊
Holy halibut
是首领
it's the Chief
谢谢你介绍我  飞毛腿
Thank you for the introduction, Quickster
可是大伙儿都认得我
but we all know who Iam
而且重点是我们得知了邪恶帮的行踪
More to the point, we've got news
on the whereabouts of EVIL
行踪是个什么宗
The whoseabouts of what?
说出他们的位置就行  首领
You just tell us where they are, Chief
我们会尽早把他们捆起来抓住的
and we'll hog-tie them faster
than you can say "salsa verde"
我们线人最近一次看到邪恶帮
Our sources last saw EVIL
在调情礁骚扰青少年
harassing teenagers up at Make-Out Reef
调情礁就那个
You know, Make-Out Reef
我的比目鱼啊  美人鱼战士
Floppin' flounder, Mermaidman
调情礁
Make-Out Reef
这些恶魔啊
Those fiends
居然袭击荷尔蒙失调的小朋友们
Attacking hormonally stressed-out children
调情礁
Make-Out Reef
真尽兴  真尽兴
Good times, good times
去调情礁
To Make-Out Reef
出发
Away
所以是不是吃不到匹萨了
Does this mean we're not getting pizza?
悬崖危险
住手
Stop it
不要骚扰我们
Leave us alone
别照了
Please, stop
求你们了
Please
约翰南茜坐树上  亲亲吻吻无处藏
John and Nancy sitting in a tree, K-I-S-S-I-N-G
用手电筒照那辆车  射线恶魔
Shine the flashlight in that car, Man Ray
好啊
With pleasure
老天爷啊  这样可不好
Hey, man, that's not cool
放过那些打情骂俏的小年轻
Leave those young lovers alone
这不是霉人鱼战士吗
Well, if it isn't Milkmaid Man
用不着费劲找你了
You've saved us the trouble of tracking you down
你们这些恶魔不会赢的
You fiends can't win
你们人少
You're outnumbered
你怕是糊涂了
You senile bag of fish paste
我们这边有三个  你那边只有一个
There are three of us and only one of you
变两个了
Make that two
飞毛腿
The Quickster
三个
Three
怒火船长
Captain Magma
四个
Four
弹性胖胖
The Elastic Waistband
五个
Five
无影小姐
M-M-Miss Appear?
加上我就是十个  吧
And me makes ten, I think
这下情况不妙了
I don't feel so good about this
我们形象的玩具要卖不出去了
There goes our toy deal
超级老相识们  出击
Super Acquaintances, attack
别
Oh, no
饶命啊
Please, mercy
喀拉喀托大爆发
Krakatoa
弄下来  弄下来
Get it off, get it off
弄下来
Get it off
我来救你  飞毛腿
I'll save you, Quickster
什么
What?
我来给你冷却  飞毛腿
I'll cool you off, Quickster
用我的水弹
with one of my water balls
不对  不对
No-no, no-no
我不是飞毛腿
I'm not the Quickster
我是怒火船
I'm Captain Mag
长
ma
看来该我上了
Well, I guess it's up to me
我隐形起来溜过去
I'll just sneak over, unseen
然后捉他们个措手不及
and catch them by surprise
悬崖危险
弄下来
Get it off
真高兴结束了
Glad that's over
我们
We
成功了  我们赢了
we did it, we won
这成功之日属于邪恶帮
This day belongs to EVIL
你输了  美人鱼战士
You've lost, Mermaidman
根据超级英雄与超级恶人的规则
And the superhero- super-villain rules say
你必须要答应我的要求
you have to give in to my demands
行  你想要什么
Okay, what do you want?
统治世界
World domination
跟他说我们要统治世界
Tell him we want world domination
我要让他吃土
And I'll make him eat dirt
首先还是要统治世界
In addition to the domination thing
第一  把我当作超级英雄
Number one: I want to be treated like a superhero
别把我当小跟班
not a sidekick
第二  要叫我企鹅男人
Number two: I want to be called Barnacleman
第三
And number three
说啊  统治世界
Come on, domination
我要成人尺寸的蟹黄堡
I want an adult-sized Krabby Patty
你有听见他说吃土吗
Did you hear him say anything about eating dirt?
要搭把手吗
Need a hand?
超级搭档
Super pal?
朋友
真高兴你又回归正义一方了  凯尔
Good to have you back on the side of justice, Kyle
我给你买蟹黄堡去
Let's go get you that Krabby Patty
居然就这
Was that it?
恶心到我了
I feel sick
这倒让我想起了
This reminds me of the time
I went to Cancún with the Killer Shrimp
我跟大虾杀手去墨西哥旅游城市坎昆
那边有木瓜饮料
They had these papaya drinks
我的海神王啊  闭嘴吧
Oh, Neptune, shut up
蟹堡王
这成人尺寸的蟹黄堡吃得怎么样
How's that adult-sized Krabby Patty treating you
企鹅男
Barnacle
人
man?
说实在的  太大了
Actually, it's pretty big
不清楚吃不吃得完
I'm not sure I can finish the whole thing